{
  "totalQuestions": 23,
  "title": "Určujeme století",
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "623",
      "answers": ["7. století", "6. století", "16. století"],
      "correctAnswer": "7. století"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "863",
      "answers": ["8. století", "9. století", "18. století"],
      "correctAnswer": "9. století"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "906",
      "answers": ["9. století", "10. století", "19. století"],
      "correctAnswer": "10. století"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "935",
      "answers": ["10. století", "9. století", "19. století"],
      "correctAnswer": "10. století"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "995",
      "answers": ["10. století", "9. století", "11. století"],
      "correctAnswer": "10. století"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "1085",
      "answers": ["11. století", "10. století", "1. století"],
      "correctAnswer": "11. století"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "1125",
      "answers": ["1. století", "10. století", "12. století"],
      "correctAnswer": "12. století"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "1212",
      "answers": ["13. století", "12. století", "2. století"],
      "correctAnswer": "13. století"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "1278",
      "answers": ["12. století", "1. století", "13. století"],
      "correctAnswer": "13. století"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "1306",
      "answers": ["14. století", "12. století", "1. století"],
      "correctAnswer": "14. století"
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "question": "1316",
      "answers": ["14. století", "15. století", "16. století"],
      "correctAnswer": "14. století"
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "question": "1348",
      "answers": ["14. století", "15. století", "3. století"],
      "correctAnswer": "14. století"
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "question": "1437",
      "answers": ["14. století", "15. století", "4. století"],
      "correctAnswer": "15. století"
    },
    {
      "id": 14,
      "question": "1415",
      "answers": ["14. století", "15. století", "4. století"],
      "correctAnswer": "15. století"
    },
    {
      "id": 15,
      "question": "1526",
      "answers": ["16. století", "15. století", "6. století"],
      "correctAnswer": "16. století"
    },
    {
      "id": 16,
      "question": "1620",
      "answers": ["16. století", "17. století", "6. století"],
      "correctAnswer": "17. století"
    },
    {
      "id": 17,
      "question": "1774",
      "answers": ["18. století", "17. století", "7. století"],
      "correctAnswer": "18. století"
    },
    {
      "id": 18,
      "question": "1781",
      "answers": ["18. století", "17. století", "16. století"],
      "correctAnswer": "18. století"
    },
    {
      "id": 19,
      "question": "1848",
      "answers": ["18. století", "19. století", "8. století"],
      "correctAnswer": "19. století"
    },
    {
      "id": 20,
      "question": "1918",
      "answers": ["18. století", "19. století", "20. století"],
      "correctAnswer": "20. století"
    },
    {
      "id": 21,
      "question": "1945",
      "answers": ["9. století", "19. století", "20. století"],
      "correctAnswer": "20. století"
    },
    {
      "id": 22,
      "question": "1968",
      "answers": ["9. století", "19. století", "20. století"],
      "correctAnswer": "20. století"
    },
    {
      "id": 23,
      "question": "2004",
      "answers": ["2. století", "20. století", "21. století"],
      "correctAnswer": "21. století"
    }
  ]
}
